{
  "cover": "/uploads/1767729801711-00.webp",
  "backCover": "/uploads/1767583329411-zz.webp",
  "pages": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "front": "/uploads/1767729957068-01.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767729807090-02.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767582277042",
      "front": "/uploads/1767730389765-03.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767730391808-04.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767600573790",
      "front": "/uploads/1767767425186-05.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767767429345-06.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767600635290",
      "front": "/uploads/1767768612949-07.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767768615248-08.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767600635447",
      "front": "/uploads/1767767461606-09.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767767464871-10.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767600635483",
      "front": "/uploads/1767767469259-11.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767767473409-12.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767600659728",
      "front": "/uploads/1767767483390-13.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767767486535-14.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767600659887",
      "front": "/uploads/1767767489704-15.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767767492673-16.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767600659918",
      "front": "/uploads/1767767495773-17.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767767498912-18.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773201938",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773212430-19.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773214728-20.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773203089",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773217676-21.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773220191-22.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773203238",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773222695-23.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773225117-24.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773203391",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773227858-25.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773230341-26.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773203538",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773233494-27.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773236236-28.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773203682",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773238951-29.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773242859-30.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773203829",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773245720-31.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773250561-32.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773203974",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773257905-33.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773260914-34.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773204115",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773264556-35.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773267343-36.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773204271",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773269786-37.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773272291-38.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773204427",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773275240-39.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773277831-40.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773204571",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773280010-41.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773282680-42.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773204719",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773285332-43.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773288007-44.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773204869",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773290721-45.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773293213-46.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773205021",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773295621-47.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773297944-48.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773301787",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773309275-49.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773312264-50.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773302240",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773314683-51.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773316832-52.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773302624",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773318969-53.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773321154-54.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773302950",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773323889-55.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773327108-56.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773303108",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773330022-57.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773332530-58.webp"
    },
    {
      "id": "1767773303433",
      "front": "/uploads/1767773334815-59.webp",
      "back": "/uploads/1767773338105-60.webp"
    }
  ],
  "width": 2000,
  "height": 3230,
  "borderRadius": "0px",
  "glossy": false,
  "staticLeft": "/uploads/1767730893119-01.webp",
  "staticRight": "/uploads/1767731112792-Ultima.webp"
}